

Contact

Phone

(+58)4148524974

Email

stx_jose@hotmail.com

Location

Puerto Ordaz, Venezuela

Links

Linkedin

GitHub

Portfolio

Skills

- HTML & CSS
- Javascript
- React
- Redux
- NodeJs
- Express Sequelize
- Postgres

Language

Spanish Native English

Jose Lezama

Profile

Experienced full stack developer with over 1 year of experience building responsive, user-friendly, and visually appealing web applications. Skilled in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, NodeJs, PosgresSql, Sequelize, AWS, Firebase and popular front-end frameworks like React-Redux. Committed to staying up-to-date with the latest technologies and best practices to provide the best user experience for clients.

Experience

Q June 2011 - April 2019

Servicios Especiales de Seguridad C.A

Manager

I was in charge of managing the administration of the company, paying taxes, among other activities.

January 2010 - April 2010

SENIAT

Intership

this is a IRS government institution in Venezuela where I did my internship in the special taxpayers area to finish my career as a Bachelor of business administration.

Education

O September 2005 - March 2010

Universidad Nororiental Gran Mariscal de Ayacucho

Bachelor

Bachelor of business administration.

June 2022 – November 2022

Bootcamp Henry

Full stack developer

Full stack webdeveloper.

Portfolio: https://portfolio-4b57a.web.app/

Extracurricular activities

Ecommerce

This is an App made for peopple who wants to buy/sell cars this was a team proyect app, where we use React. Redux, CSS/Tailwind, cloudinary to upload images at front, Mercado Pago to make payments, auth0 for authentication, PostgresSQL/Sequelize for the database and Railway for deployment. https://carsmarket.vercel.app

Pokemon-App Videogames-App

2 single web App where you can find all your favorite pokemons or videogames using filters or the seaarchBar. Technologies: HTML/CSS, React, Redux at front, Expres, Sequeleze, PostgresSQL for the database and AWS / Vercel for deployment https://pokemon-xi-green.vercel.app - https://videogames-beta.vercel.app

Single Web Page

This is a well made exibition web page simulating a healthy food proyect using HTML/CSS https://omnii-foood.netlify.app

Certifications

Full stack developer

Extras

Cert Link

Cert Link

Google Activate HTML/CSS

Google Drive Link HTML
Google Drive Link CSS